（夢子(ゆめこ)）鈴井(すずい)さん
Suzui, good morning.
おはようございます
（鈴井）
あっ 蛇喰(じゃばみ)さん おはよう
Hey, Yumeko. Good morning!
あら 嫌ですわ
Oh, how disappointing.
私たち
お友達になりましたでしょう？
You and I are friends now, aren't we?
（鈴井）え？
（夢子）夢子 でいいですよ
You may call me Yumeko.
（鈴井）
ん!? あっ うん あ〜 その…
Right! Okay.
夢子… には
Yumeko, I really owe you big-time, huh?
とんでもない借りが
出来ちゃったな
（夢子）え？
What?
Yesterday's...
（鈴井）
昨日の… すぐには無理だけど
必ず返すから
I can't pay you back right away,
but I promise I will.
（夢子）
ウッフフ
あれは差し上げた物ですから
That was a gift,
so please don't give it another thought.
気になさらないでください
Well, not that I have any hopes
of paying it back.
あっ 確かに 返す当てはないけど
って いやいや そういうわけには
Wait. No, I can't let you do that!
（夢子）あ…
（鈴井）あっ！
UGLY, FLAT CHEST, TINY BREASTS, DIE
（生徒たちの笑い声）
（夢子）早乙女(さおとめ)さん これは一体？
Saotome, what is the meaning of this?
What happened?
何かあったのですか？
これってイジメ…
- Is this bully--?
- Shut up!
（芽亜里(めあり)）うるさい！
（夢子）あっ
あんたに負けたから
こうなってんだよ！
- This happened because I lost to you!
- Come on, put your name tag on.
（生徒Ａ）
こ〜ら 早く名札付けなきゃ！
（生徒Ｂ）
ルール違反で 借金増えちゃうよ
If you violate the rules,
it'll add to your debt.
（生徒Ｃ）ミ〜ケ ミ〜ケ！
Mittens!
（芽亜里）くっ…
（生徒たち）
ミ〜ケ ミ〜ケ ミ〜ケ ミ〜ケ…
（鈴井）
私立 百花王(ひゃっかおう)学園
Hyakkao Private Academy.
この名門校には階級制度がある
A hierarchy exists
at this prestigious school.
それを決めるのは
勉強やスポーツではない
It's not grades or athletic prowess
that gets you to the top.
ただ ギャンブルの強さのみ
Just your gambling skills, nothing else.
〜
（鈴井）
早乙女のことは
君のせいじゃないよ
What happened to Mary isn't your fault.
この学園のルールなんだ
- It's just the rule at this academy.
- Rule?
（夢子）ルール？
Yeah.
（鈴井）うん
うちって政財界の
実力者の家の子が多いからさ
A lot of students are from families
of political and business leaders.
将来 人を使う人間に必要なのは
駆け引きとか読心術
If you're gonna rule over others someday,
you need negotiating skills,
the ability to read people's minds,
あと ここぞってときの勝負強さ
っていうのが学園の考え方なんだ
and also, the ability to come through
when it counts.
- That's the academy's philosophy.
- Oh.
（夢子）はあ
だからここじゃ
That's why at this school,
the skilled gamblers are the most popular.
ギャンブルが強い人が
人望を集めるし
Those who aren't become
the object of oppression.
逆に弱いと
迫害の対象になることもある
具体的には階級制度があって
Specifically, there's a hierarchy here.
STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM
学園のギャンブルを 一元的に
管理している生徒会への上納金
Donations are made to the student council,
which controls all the gambling.
その金額で階級が決するんだ
The amount you donate
determines your rank.
ランキングは不定期に発表されて
Rankings are announced
on an irregular basis.
そこで全生徒３千人中
下位100位になると
If you're in the bottom 100
of the 3,000-strong student body,
非協力傾向生徒
通称“家畜”とされる
you become a non-cooperative student,
a house pet.
Your name is "Fido" if you're male,
家畜の名前は 男ならポチ
女ならミケって決まってる
"Mittens" if you're female.
（夢子）
あっ じゃあ 鈴井さんのも…
Oh, so you also...
Yeah. But thanks to a special donation
of one million, I got that revoked.
うん でも100万の特別上納金で
解除されたんだ
Thanks to you.
君のおかげでね
Oh, my. Congratulations, then.
まあ それは
おめでとうございます
Thank you from the bottom of--
（鈴井）本当にありが…
（生徒）うわ！
（２人）アッハッハッハ
（生徒）うっ はあ あ…
It didn't used to be this bad.
（鈴井）
昔はここまで
ひどくなかったけど…
変わったのは２年前
Everything changed two years ago,
今の生徒会長が就任してからだ
after the current
student council president took office.
Kirari Momobami.
桃喰(ももばみ)綺羅莉(きらり)
うちは中高一貫だけど
彼女は高等部で編入してきた
This academy combines
junior high and high school,
but she transferred into the high school.
で いきなり生徒会長になったんだ
She became student council president
right off the bat
当時の生徒会長と
by gambling with the previous president
for the position.
会長の座を賭けた
ギャンブルをして…
（夢子）
まあ 会長の座をギャンブルで？
Oh, my! She became president by gambling?
The members of our student council
are all elite gamblers.
（鈴井）
この学園の生徒会って
最強のギャンブル集団だからね
そのトップに勝つって相当だよ
To beat the best of them is mind-blowing.
She started pushing through reforms.
彼女は改革を断行
上納金やポチミケ制は
このとき出来たんだ
That's when the donation
and Fido-Mittens systems were created.
それからだよ
That's when it started.
どんどん差別意識が
強くなっていったのは
When the discrimination intensified.
Well, Mary's case is extreme.
まあ 早乙女の場合は極端だけど
みんなに協力させたあげく
こっぴどく負けたからな
But she roped everyone into her scheme,
then suffered a crushing defeat.
上納金の締め日が重なったのも
運が悪かったとしか…
For it to happen on the same day
as donation deadlines, that's bad luck.
Oh, sorry. Did all that talk scare you?
あっ ごめん
怖がらせちゃったかな？
Seriously, the more I hear about it,
the more fringe this academy is.
全く…
聞けば聞くほど
規格外の学園ですね
はあ
ああ！
転校してきて よかったです
I'm so glad that I transferred here.
Doesn't this girl ever feel fear?
（鈴井）
この子には
恐怖って感情はないのか？
（生徒たちの歓声）
（鈴井）あっ
（伊月(いつき)）フルハウス 私の勝ちね！
Full house. That means I win!
エヘヘ よっしゃ！
Score!
（夢子）
わあ お昼休みにも
ギャンブル やってるんですね
Oh, so there's gambling going on
during recess, too?
（鈴井）うん あっ！
Yeah. Oh!
That girl's only a first-year,
but she's a member of the student council.
あの子 １年生にして
生徒会役員やってる—
ちょっと有名な子だよ
- She's kind of famous.
- Then she gambled for her position, too?
じゃあ やっぱりギャンブルで？
（鈴井）
いや 多額の上納金だって
うわさなんだ
No, rumor has it
she donated a lot of money.
何でも日本有数のトイメーカーの
社長令嬢なんだって
I hear she's the daughter
of one of Japan's biggest toy makers.
半端ない金持ちで
ギャンブルの腕も立つ
She's filthy rich
and a skilled gambler, as well.
特にトランプでは
無敗なんて話も…
Especially at cards,
they say she's undefeated.
Undefeated? Well, that's amazing!
無敗？ それはすごいですね！
- I would love to play her--
- Don't even think about it!
ぜひ一度 お手合わせを…
（鈴井）
いや いや いや
やめといたほうが…
（伊月）蛇喰先輩
Yumeko-senpai?
LAME GIRL
はじめまして 私 １年華組
皇(すめらぎ) 伊月と申します
Nice to meet you! I'm Itsuki Sumeragi
of Year One, Flower Class.
以後 お見知りおきを
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
What's this all of a sudden?
（鈴井）な… 何だい いきなり
先輩 話題になってますよ〜
Senpai, everyone's talking about you.
I hear you wiped the floor
with Mary-senpai on your first day.
何でも転校初日に早乙女先輩を
ギッタギタにしたとか
実は 私もギャンブルには
自信がありまして
I'm confident of my own gambling skills.
I wanted to see how we stack up.
比べてみるのも面白いかなって
ええ ぜひ
- Yes, I'd love to!
- Hey, Yumeko!
ちょっ… 夢子！
That's what I like to hear!
そうこなくっちゃ イヒッ
Damn, garbage again.
（生徒）ああ またブタだよ
（芽亜里）
なんで 私が こんな… なんで
- I'm not falling for that again!
- Why is this happening to me? Why?
どうして こんなことに…
How did it come to this? Why me?
私が
私が… なんで
Why me? Why?
（ガチャ！）
（生徒）あっ ミケ
Darn. Mittens, I spilled my coffee.
コーヒーこぼしちゃった
掃除しておいて
Clean up the mess, all right?
くっ…
うっ…
（男子生徒）おい 大変だ！
Hey, guess what?
生徒会の皇 伊月が
ギャンブルやるぞ！
Sumeragi from the student council
is gonna gamble!
（女子生徒）え〜 相手は？
What? Who's her opponent?
何と 我らが蛇喰夢子！
You won't believe this. Yumeko Jabami!
No way!
（生徒たち）
マジかよ！
えっ どこどこ？
- Where?
- The cafeteria, I hear.
食堂だって
（遠ざかる生徒たちの足音）
So, about the type of gambling
we'll be doing...
で ギャンブルの種類なんですけど
How do you feel
about Double Concentration?
ダブル神経衰弱なんてどうですか？
As its name implies,
we're going to use two decks.
その名のとおり
デックを２つ 使用するんです
普通の神経衰弱は
数字が同じなら当たりですが
In Normal Concentration,
we match numbers,
これはマークも同じでないと
当たりと認めません
but in this game,
we match both number and suit.
つまり 総カードは倍の104枚で
There are twice as many cards than usual,
but only one pair of matching cards.
当たりは
たったの１組だけなんです
I see. That sounds fun!
なるほど 面白いですね
ぜひ やりましょう
- I'd love to play.
- Okay.
（伊月）オッケー
では 肝心の賭け金ですが
Now, about how much we bet...
生徒会発行の
100万円チップ 20枚
Twenty-one million yen chips
issued by the student council.
２千万でどうでしょう？
What about 20 million yen?
ああ
Unfortunately, I no longer have
that much money on me.
残念ですが 私の手元には もう
そんなにお金は残っていないのです
とても２千万なんて
用意できません
I can't possibly raise 20 million yen.
What? You don't look like
such a spendthrift.
へえ 見かけによらず
金遣い荒いんですね
それとも借金でもあったとか？
Or wait, maybe you had some debt?
（鈴井）え？ あっ ごっ ごめん
Sorry.
でも 心配ご無用
No need to worry.
I'll lend you 20 million at zero interest.
貸しますよ２千万 無利子で
（鈴井）
え？ な… 何のメリットがあって
そんなこと…
What would you gain from that?
To be honest,
20 million is nothing to me.
正直 ２千万くらい
そこまで痛くもないんですよ
それより みんなが
我が社のトランプに
There's far more value to be had if you
take an interest in our company's cards.
興味を持ってくれるほうが
よほど価値がある
広報活動の一環ですね
It's part of my PR duties.
そういうことでしたら
ぜひ お願いします
In that case, I accept.
Okay. So, this gamble is on, right?
オッケー ギャンブル成立ですね
先ほどの説明どおり
新品のトランプを２つ用意します
As I explained just now,
I'm breaking out
two brand-new decks of cards.
うちの主力製品 ラクレット
Our leading product, Raclette!
日本で２番目に売れてる
トランプなんですよ
It's the second-most popular brand
in Japan!
手になじむ使いやすさが
売りです〜
They fit in your hand like a glove!
I hope you buy them!
よろしくお願いしますね
（鈴井）ホントに宣伝すんのか…
（伊月）お薦めですよ〜
She's really selling them, huh?
ダブル神経衰弱 始めましょう
Double Concentration. Let's begin!
どうぞ先輩 先手は譲りますよ
After you, senpai.
You can make the opening move.
（夢子）あら それはどうも
I appreciate that. I suppose it won't do
any good to hesitate on the first move.
う〜ん 初手で迷っても
しかたありませんね
どちらも４ですが このルールだと
当たりではないわけですね
They're both fours,
but this doesn't count as a match, right?
That's correct. My turn next, right?
Looking for a four of hearts or diamonds!
そのとおり
次は私ですね
ハートかダイヤの４狙い
（鈴井）
やっぱり このゲーム
難しすぎないか？
This game is too hard, isn't it?
当たりが１枚きりってことは
If there's only one matching pair,
運で当たりを引ける可能性は
103分の１しかない
the odds of achieving it through luck
are one in 103.
とすれば 既に開かれたカードを
覚えるしかないわけだけど
Your only hope is to memorize the cards
that have already been drawn.
103枚のカードを
覚えきれるわけもない
But there's no way
anyone can memorize 103 cards.
ダイヤのキングに
スペードのエース
King of diamonds, ace of spades.
あれがハートの２で
あの角がクラブの…
The two of hearts,
and the one in the corner's a club...
ダメだ 頭 痛くなってきた
I'm getting a headache.
The four of diamonds showed up
before, right? Where was it?
あっ ダイヤの４って出たよな
場所は…
I believe it was over here. I got it!
確か ここでしたね
やった！
（伊月）
当たりは続けて引けます
どうぞ
When you get a match, keep going.
ダイヤの７
Seven of diamonds.
クラブのキング 外れです
King of clubs. Not a match.
おっ クラブのキングは
見覚えありますね
I remember seeing the king of clubs.
ここだ！
Here it is!
（生徒Ａ）うわ！
（生徒Ｂ）皇も負けてないな
Sumeragi's holding her own, huh?
Unbelievable. It's a close match.
（鈴井）
すごい… 接戦だ
夢子が18枚 皇が22枚
Yumeko has 18. Sumeragi's got 22.
Neither is losing ground to the other.
どちらも譲らない
Maybe it's just me, but neither one
has messed up once, right?
（男子生徒）
なあ 気のせいかもだけど
さっきから２人共 ノーミスだよな
（女子生徒）どういうこと？
What do you mean?
いや だから
一度開いたカードを引いたとき
It seems like
after they've flipped over a card once,
確実に当ててる気がするんだけど
they're matching it without fail.
（女子生徒）は？
ハートの５…
Five of hearts,
I've already seen this one.
これは もう見ました
（歓声）
（男子生徒）やっぱりそうだよ！
I'm telling you, I'm right!
（女子生徒）
開いたカードの場所
全部 覚えてんの？
They remember every card
that's been flipped over?
（鈴井）
記憶力は互角
In terms of memory, they're equal.
となると
This is a contest of luck, whether
they can draw a card they've already seen.
あとは 一度開いたカードを
引けるかどうかの運の勝負だ
残りは28枚
Twenty-eight cards left. Yumeko has 36.
夢子が36枚
Sumeragi has 40.
It's still too close to call.
皇 40枚で 依然 接戦
でも ここからは厳しいぞ
It's gonna be rough from here on out.
残りの枚数が減れば
それだけ当たりやすくなる
The fewer cards there are,
the easier it'll be to match them.
きっと ゲームが動く
The game's sure to take a turn now.
ウフッ
やりますね 先輩
I'm impressed, senpai.
I've never felt so challenged before.
こんなにいい勝負になったの
初めてです
Oh, please. I'm honored.
あら そんな… 光栄です
I'd better bear down now.
（伊月）
私も気を引き締めないと…
あっ 当たりです
Hey, a match. And this one is here.
で これが こう… 当たりっと
A match.
Moving on, this one's...
更に これが… よし！
All right! I've seen this one before, too.
お！ これも見ましたね
ああ…
Hey.
Oh, wow.
おや？
Ten in a row.
10枚 連取！
Looks like the goddess of good fortune
is on my side.
どうやら幸運の女神は
私に ほほ笑んでいるようですね
（鈴井）
夢子との差は14枚
ここで この差は もう…
That's a 14-card lead over Yumeko.
She can't possibly close the gap now.
Oh, no.
（伊月）あっと… 外れ
That's a miss. Go on, senpai.
どうぞ 先輩
次 外したらもう…
If you miss the next one,
I'm afraid I'm going to end up winning.
勝っちゃいますよ きっと
頑張ってくださいね〜
Please give it your all!
あっ…
She missed.
（鈴井）
外した…
（生徒たち）ああ！
（伊月）はい 当たり！
That's a match. I've matched 54 pairs,
more than half the deck, meaning I've won.
これで過半数54枚出たので
私の勝利ですね
Right?
（生徒たち）
わあ〜！
すっげ〜な
（鈴井）
夢子… ２千万の借金
どうすんだ？
Yumeko, you're 20 million yen in the hole.
What are you gonna do?
You said yourself
you didn't have that kind of money.
そんな大金 持ってないって
言ってたのに…
（伊月）
アッハハ やった〜
また勝ったよ！
- I won again!
- Sumeragi.
（夢子）皇さん…
（伊月）は？
もう１戦 もう１戦だけ
やっていただけませんか？
Would you mind playing me
just one more time?
（伊月）え…
I can't possibly repay 20 million!
２千万なんて とても払えません！
私もあなたと同じく
I had all of the flipped-over cards
memorized, just as you had.
開いたカードの位置は
全部 覚えていたんです！
こんな形で負けるなんて
納得いきません！
To lose in such a manner,
I can't accept it. One more match, please.
もう一度だけ 勝負してください！
フッ
実は 私…
The thing is,
I have a thing for collecting nails.
ネイルのコレクションが
趣味なんです
う…
（伊月）ほら かわいいでしょ？
Look! Aren't they adorable?
Needless to say,
this is only part of my collection.
もちろん こんなの
ほんの一部ですよ
で 実は これには
ちょっとした秘密がありまして〜
And there's actually a little secret
to these nails.
You see, these are all real nails.
これ 全部 生爪なんです
（雷鳴）
はっ！
My, my.
（伊月）あら… アッハハハ
お金で買えたら楽なんですけど
It'd make my life easier
if I could buy them,
み〜んな なかなか
売ってくれないから
but people loath selling them to me,
ほとんどは ギャンブルで
ぶんどった物なんです
so most of these are the ones
I plundered through gambling.
ってことで
こちらが２千万賭けるなら
Therefore,
if I were to bet 20 million yen...
ああ〜 先輩
Oh, senpai.
私 その爪 欲しいな〜
I'd love to have those nails of yours.
（雷鳴）
う… うそだろ？ 爪を賭けるって
You're kidding, right?
Put her nails on the line?
フフッ どうですか 先輩？
What do you say, senpai?
ゆ… 夢子
Yumeko, there's no need to accept
these ridiculous terms--
こんなバカな条件
受け入れる必要…
分かりました　それで結構です
Very well. That's acceptable to me.
な！ ちょっ 何言って…
Hold up, what are you--?
I have to! There's no other way
for me to repay my debt.
だって これしか
お金を返す方法がないんですもの
それとも鈴井さんが
払ってくださるとでも？
Unless you're going
to pay it off for me, Suzui?
（鈴井）え？ いや それは…
No, that's not...
（伊月）アハッ そうこなくっちゃ
That's the right attitude!
新品のカードを使いますね
Let's use brand-new cards, all right?
- Is this for real?
- My heart's pounding!
（生徒たち）
うそだろ？
何か ドキドキしてきた
（鈴井）
むちゃくちゃだ
This is insane.
いくら この学園でも
Even at this school,
there's hardly ever any gambling
that involves bodily injury.
肉体的損傷を伴うギャンブルなんて
めったにない
それだけに みんな 興奮している
No wonder everyone's getting pumped up.
冗談じゃ済まないぞ
This is no laughing matter.
（伊月）では 始めましょうか？
Shall we begin?
The stakes are 20 million yen for me.
賭け金は 私が２千万
先輩が 手足の爪
For you, senpai,
your fingernails and toenails!
で いいですね？
- That all right with you?
- Yes.
（夢子）はい
（伊月）
では 今回も 先手をどうぞ
Please go first again, senpai.
（夢子）ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
（伊月）
アハッ ま〜た
コレクションが増えちゃった
I've added to my collection yet again.
After all, I've got this match in the bag.
今回も私が 絶対 勝つもんね
だって
Because I know
what half of the hidden cards are.
私 伏せカードの半分 52枚
何のカードか 分かってるんだもん
このトランプ
These cards, at a glance,
are indistinguishable
一見 流通している正規品と
変わらないけど
from the genuine product in the shops.
実は 個人的に作ったラインで
生産している別のトランプ
But they're a different line I had
produced separately for my personal use.
正規品とは１つだけ
違うところがある
There's just one thing
that sets them apart.
一定以上の温度で
模様が浮き出るんだ
The pattern stands out
above a certain temperature.
かばんにはカイロが
仕込んであるから
Since my bag is rigged with hand warmers,
after I've laid them out,
こうやって並べたあと
冷めるまで２〜３分
for two to three minutes, until they cool,
the pattern remains visible.
浮き出た模様は 残り続ける
細かい変化だし すぐ消えるから
バレっこない
After a minute, it disappears.
There's no way anyone can catch on.
私はそれを覚えてるってわけ
I remember all the positions, you see.
So how could I possibly lose?
負けるはずないよね〜
ダブル神経衰弱にしたのは
The reason I chose Double Concentration
was to raise the difficulty level
and protect against lucky guesses.
難易度を上げて
ラッキーパンチを防ぐため
カードの中身が分かれば
As long as I know each card, I'm sure
to win, whether it's poker or Old Maid.
ポーカーでもババ抜きでも
まず勝てる
覚えるのは苦労したけど
リターンは大きかった
It was a struggle memorizing them all,
but the returns were substantial.
ウフッ 先輩 その爪 頂き！
Senpai, those nails are mine!
（伊月）うっ！
（女子生徒）当たりだ！
- A match!
- She lucked out from the start.
（男子生徒）
しょっぱなからラッキーだな
ときに皇さん ご実家は
有名なトイメーカーだそうですね
By the way, Sumeragi, I hear your family
runs a famous toy manufacturer.
Excuse me?
はい？
（夢子）そんな大きな企業
What's the total market value
of such a large company, I wonder?
時価総額は いくらくらいに
なるのでしょうか？
100億 それとも
１千億くらい いきますか？
Ten billion?
Or closer to 100 billion yen, perhaps?
対して このギャンブルは
２千万ですよね？
This gamble
is worth 20 million yen, correct?
割に合わないのではないですか？
It hardly seems worth it.
- What are you talking about?
- A word of advice for you.
何のこと？
（夢子）
ひとつ ご忠告
申し上げましょう
ご実家の稼業を
賭けるような真似(まね)は
If you're gonna put
your family's company on the line,
それなりの覚悟を
なさってからにしましょうね
first make sure
that you're sufficiently prepared.
（伊月）
は？ 何を言っている
What's that? My family?
私の実家？
はっ！
ま… まさか こいつ
Don't tell me she's...
She's seen through my trickery!
イカサマに気付いた…？
Is she threatening me?
私を脅しているのか？
確かにトイメーカー 自ら
If a toy company were to be exposed
as producing trick decks,
イカサマカードを作ってる
なんてバレたら
the scandal would run it into the ground!
会社が傾く不祥事だ
（夢子）フッ
（伊月）はっ！
How much does she know?
（伊月）
どこまで 気付かれている？
消えかけの模様を見つけたか？
Did she spot the disappearing patterns?
No, it's possible
that this is just a bluff.
いや もしかしたら
ブラフという可能性も… ダメだ！
No! Now that it's come to this,
as soon as it's my turn,
こうなったら 私の番で
一気にカードを開いて
I'll retrieve the cards when I flip them
and switch them out with normal cards.
すぐ回収する
そして普通のデックとすり替える
もう これしかない 私の番に…
That's my only hope now.
When it's my turn... When my turn comes...
When my turn comes... When my...
私の番になったら
私の番になったら 私の…
Yumeko.
ゆ… 夢子
（生徒たち）あ〜
これで54枚
That makes 54. Meaning I win, right?
私の勝ちですね
は？
え？ うそ… なんで…
No way. How?
ウッフフ
あなたが もう少し用心深ければ
私の負けでした
If you'd only been more cautious,
I would've lost.
Because... the patterns on the back
are the same as before, aren't they?
だって…
裏の模様が 先ほどと
同じではないですか？
あなたが もう１組
If you'd used another deck
that showed a different pattern,
別の模様が浮かぶデックを
用意していれば
お手上げでしたのに
- I would've had to give up.
- You mean you had them all memorized?
（伊月）
は？
お… 覚えてたっていうのか！
もし そうなら こいつは
If that's true, then this girl
must've been aware of the patterns
１回目のゲーム開始から
模様を認識していたってことになる
from the start.
She pretended not to notice
and kept playing.
知らぬふりをして
ゲームを続けたんだ
Her bitterness after losing
was all an act.
負けたと悔しがってたのも 演技？
でも それにしたって
Even so, those patterns are only visible
for two or three minutes.
模様が出るのは
ほんの２〜３分だぞ
その間に全ての模様を覚え
In that time,
she memorized all the patterns
and matched the patterns to the faces
of the cards that got flipped over.
かつ そのあと開かれた
カードの中身と模様を結び付ける
Is that even humanly possible?
そんなことが人間に可能なのか？
（伊月）ひっ！
（夢子）さあ
We're done with this game now.
Let's move on to the next one.
このゲームは これでおしまい
次にいきましょ 次！
（伊月）は？
（夢子）何をします？
What shall we play? Blackjack?
Or baccarat, perhaps?
ブラックジャック？
それともバカラ？
（伊月）いや… 私は もう…
No, I'm good.
My, my,
are you in any position to decline?
あら〜 断れるお立場でしたか？
（伊月）ひっ！
（夢子）あっ そうだ！
Oh, right.
This time,
why don't we each stake our nails?
今度は お互い
生爪を賭けませんか？
“負けたら相手の手足の爪を
全部剥ぐ”ということで
Whoever loses has to rip off all
of the other's fingernails and toenails.
But... No...
あなたが要求してきたこと
なのだから かまいませんね？
You requested such stakes,
so you don't mind, right?
爪剥ぎは術後がつらいといいます
They say it's agony
after your nails are torn off.
指に負担をかける度に
血がにじむとか…
Every time you exert pressure
on your fingers, there's blood.
それを手足全部ですから
日常生活が困難になるでしょうね
Since we're talking all of your nails,
I'm sure it'll hinder your everyday life.
To play with so much on the line...
そんなリスクを賭けた真剣勝負
想像するだけで…
Just thinking about it makes me smolder!
たぎってしまいます！
Now, then, Sumeragi!
さあ 皇さん！
This is the chance of a lifetime!
今が千載一遇の好機です！
The shame of defeat after rigging this
treacherous game with such confidence.
自信満々に
イカサマを仕掛けておいて
あっさり負けてしまうという汚名
ここで返上しなければ
どうするのですか！
If you don't redeem yourself now,
when will you?
やりましょう
Let's do it. All you have to do now
is nod yes. Now, then! Come on!
あとは
あなたが うなずくだけです！
さあ ほら 早く！
Hurry up!
（伊月）ぎゃ〜！
うっ うっ ぐっ うう…
むむ… 無理です ぐっ うっ
I can't.
できません
It's not possible.
うう…
うっ ゆ… 許してください
Please forgive me.
う…
は？
う… ゆ… 許して
Please forgive me.
（鈴井）
ゆ… 夢子
ここまで言ってるんだし
Yumeko, can't you see she's pleading?
つまんないの…
What a buzzkill.
うっ！
（伊月の泣き声）
（生徒たちのヒソヒソ声）
And that's the story.
（清華(さやか)）と… いう次第でした
（ユメミ）
キャハ 転入早々
皇ちゃんに勝つなんて
Taking Sumeragi down so soon after
transferring here. What an amazing girl!
すっごい子だね！
（妄(みだり)）エッヘ
雑魚に勝って 調子こいてそう
I bet she's full of herself,
beating a peon.
She only got into the student council
because of a huge donation, anyway.
（百合子(ゆりこ)）
まあ 所詮 多額の上納金で
生徒会に入っただけの方ですからね
（るな）
ニャハハ あれ
推薦したの誰だったっけな？
Hey, wait?
Who was it that recommended her again?
（豆生田(まにゅうだ)）うるさい 黙れ
Not another word.
Now, then, about this Yumeko Jabami,
how shall we dispose of her?
さて この蛇喰夢子ですが
どう始末をつけましょうか？
This is pretty intriguing.
Why don't we do some meddling?
（綺羅莉）面白いじゃない
ちょっかい出してみましょうか？
（鐘の音）
（鈴井）
ねっ ねえ 本気？
まだやるの？
Are you serious? You're not done gambling?
（夢子）
だって あれで終わりじゃ
まるで生殺しですもの
Stopping now
would be like being left in limbo.
鈴井さん おっしゃってましたよね
Suzui, didn't you tell me yourself?
That there's gambling going on everywhere.
放課後は
あちこちで賭場が立つって
Where do I go? Join me, Suzui.
どこですか？
鈴井さんも一緒に行きましょう！
あっ…
（会員）伝統文化研究会へようこそ
Welcome
to the Traditional Culture Research Club.
お客様 ただいま 折よく
公式戦が行われております
Esteemed guests,
fortunately, there's an official match
in progress right now.
ご観覧されていかれては
いかがでしょう？
Would you care to observe
while you're here?
公式戦？
Official match?
ハア ハア ハア ハア
（熊楠(くまぐす)）判定は“死”
The ruling is... death!
早乙女様
Saotome, this match has concluded
with you on the hook for 49.6 million yen.
合計4960万のマイナスで
決着です！
Forty-nine million?
（鈴井）よ… ４千！
（百合子）
早乙女さん 回収方法は
追って ご連絡 差し上げますわ
Saotome, we will contact you regarding
our collection methods at a later date.
誰か外へお連れして
Somebody please show her outside.
As I have no more use for her.
もう 用済みですから
うわ〜！
〜
（熊楠）
さあ 張った 張った！
All right, place your bets!
（百合子）
そんな怖い顔 なさらないで
- Don't look at me with a scary face!
- Every chip on life is 30 million yen!
（夢子）
あなたのやり方は最低ですけど
I'll kill you, literally.
（百合子）
文字どおり 殺して差し上げます
EPISODE 3: SLIT-EYED WOMAN